Walt Coburn papers, 1923-1977
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Works, 1923-1977
  - Magazines, 1923-1977
    - Walt Coburn's Western Magazine
      - "Outlawed!" 2/8: 14-40. May 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 2/8: 10-12. May 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Outlawed Orphan," 2/4: 12-41. June 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 2/4: 81. June 1950 (Box 12)
      - "The Death Maverick," 3/1: 12-39. July 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 3/1: 6-8. July 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Trigger-Fever!" 3/3: 12-48. November 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 3/3: 10. November 1950 (Box 12)
      - "Head-Money Man," 3/4: 4-41. January 1951 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 3/4: 111-114. January 1951 (Box 12)
      - "Stranger, Keep Riding!" 4/1: 4-39. February 1951 (Box 12)
      - "The Man From Black Coulee," 4/2: 4-35. March 1951 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 4/2: 110-113. March 1951 (Box 12)
      - "Ride Home to the Badlands," 4/3: 4-42. April 1951 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 4/3: 107-109. April 1951 (Box 12)
      - "Poison Water!" 4/4: 8-42. June 1951 (Box 12)
      - "Walt's Tally Book," 4/4: 4-7. June 1951 (Box 12)
    - Western Winners
      - "The Gloomy Outlaw," 38-61. February 1935 (Box 12)
      - "Crutcher's Cabin," 1/2: 1-49. March 1935 (Box 12)
      - "Chico," 1/3: 37-83. April 1935 (Box 12)
      - "Ride and Tie," 1/4: 59-91. May 1935 (Box 12)
      - "The Branding of a Tenderfoot," 1/5: 1-52. June 1935 (Box 12)
      - "Man on the Dun," 1/6: 1-41. July 1935 (Box 12)
      - "Survival of Slim," 2/1: 66-84. August 1935 (Box 12)
      - "Strained Honey," 2/2: 37-47. September 1935 (Box 12)
      - "A Sure-enough Paint Hoss," 2/5: 78-86. December 1935 (Box 12)
      - "Silent Saunders Pays," 2/6: 44-49. January 1936 (Box 12)
      - "Bill Talks Big," 3/1: 90-96. February 1936 (Box 12)
      - "Sin and Solitude," 60-68. March 1936 (Box 12)
      - "Riding Pretty," 49-70. 1936 (Box 12)
    - Western Story Magazine
      - "Some Sheep and a Shave," XXX/1: 95-101. November 4, 1922 (Box 13)
      - "The Man on the Dun," XXXIII/6: 3-31. April 14, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Silent Saunders Pays for Two," 103-107. May 19, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Sin and Solitude," XXXIV/6: 86-93. May 26, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "A Pal to the Last," 127-133. July 21, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Shifted Shirts," 67-74. August 4, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Triple Cross for Danger," XXXVI/5: 77-101. August 11, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Ride and Tie," XXXVII/4: 28-61. September 15, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Strained Honey," 108-118. September 22, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Bill Talks Big," 128-133. October 20, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "The Back Trail," XXXIX/1: 3-34. November 17, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "The Writing on the Rocks," 128-135. December 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Peaceful Pete's Yuletide Party," 40-47. December 22, 1923 (Box 13)
      - "Waitin' for the Coffee to Boil," XL/3: 78-91. January 12, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "The Branding of Tenderfoot," XL/5: 28-66. January 26, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "Beans for the Wolf," 44-51. February 1924 (Box 13)
      - "The Shadow's Shadow," 91-109. February 16, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "When the Wild Roses Bloom," XLI/4: 50-72. March 1, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "A Dog and a Guess," XLII/2: 99-107. March 29, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "A Sure-enough 'Paint' Hoss," 93-100. April 1924 (Box 13)
      - "The Survival of Slim," XLIII/1: 48-64. May 3, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "Bert and Sandy Pay," 52-62. June 28, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "A Generous Captor," 82-91. July 26, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "The Secret of Crutcher's Cabin," XLVI/3: 3-52. September 20, 1924 (Box 13)
      - "Chico," XLIX/5: 1-38. February 7, 1925 (Box 13)
      - "Longhorn Law," LXXVII/6: 1-36. May 5, 1928 (Box 13)
      - "Young Courage," 1-26. June 15, 1929 (Box 13)
      - "Out of the Dark," 1-24. July 20, 1929 (Box 13)
      - "Brimstone and Peace," 1-39. 1930 (Box 13)
      - "Wet Cattle," XCIV/6: 1-33. April 19, 1930 (Box 13)
      - "Valley Squatter," 1-37. June 21, 1930 (Box 13)
      - "Teh Square Shooter," 1-24. August 16, 1930 (Box 13)
      - "The Devil's Pitchfork," 1-36. September 1930 (Box 13)
      - "His Mother's Brand," 1-16. October 11, 1930 (Box 13)
      - "Wanted Men," 2-49. May 30, 1931 (Box 13)
      - "Gun Grudge," 2-23. May 7, 1932 (Box 13)
      - "Fightin' Fools," 2-454. September 3, 1932 (Box 13)
      - "Thumbs Down," CXVII/2: 2-46. November 12, 1932 (Box 13)
      - "Sleeper Marked," 2-46. December 24, 1932 (Box 13)
      - "The Fighting Farley's," CXVIII/5: 37-70. January 14, 1933 (Box 13)
      - "Bullets in the Black," 90-98. March 18, 1933 (Box 13)
      - "The Burnt Ranch," CXX/4: 4-74. April 1, 1933 (Box 13)
      - "Rope Law," CXXI/4: 6-75. May 13, 1933 (Box 13)
      - "Cayuse," CXXII/3: 5-69. June 17, 1933 (Box 13)
      - "Bait for Boothill," 8-51. February 19, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Killers of Coyote Pass," 6-33. March 19, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Gun-Lords of Tortilla Range," 6-29. April 16, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Pack Rat Killer," 6-26. May 21, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Pasear to Sombrero Butte," 8-29. June 4, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Quick Trigger Law," 8-33. July 9, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Killers of the Carrizo," 8-31. September 10, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Rustlers of the Honda," CLXVIII/5: 9-30. October 15, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Badlands Buscadero," 10-30. November 19, 1938 (Box 13)
      - "Traitor's Brand," 10-34. January 14, 1939 (Box 13)
      - "Range Orphan," 10-44. February 11, 1939 (Box 13)
      - "Brand Changers of Outlaws' Pass," 58-84. March 18, 1939 (Box 13)
      - "The Saga of Big Callio," 9-43. May 6, 1939 (Box 13)
      - "Heir to the Anchor Brand," 9-39. May 27, 1939 (Box 13)
      - "Riders of Ghost Trail," 7-38. July 15, 1939 (Box 13)
      - "Nesters at Witch Creek," 10-42. September 2, 1939 (Box 13)
      - "Gun Wolves of the Badlands," 10-45. November 11, 1939 (Box 13)
      - "Hungry Loops Swing Wide," 52-72. January 13, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Alias Rawhide Jones," 9-49. February 3, 1949 (Box 13)
      - "Repping for Satan," 10-49. February 3, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Renegade Legions," 9-47. April 27, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Range of No Return," 9-50. June 15, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Branded Arrow Pointed North," 9-47. July 13, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Code of a Maverick," 9-51. August 17, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Gun Ghosts from Tres Marias," 9-49. September 21, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Spawn of the Forbidden Valley," 9-48. November 9, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Red Wolf of Palomilla," 9-47. November 30, 1940 (Box 13)
      - "Gun Boss of Powder River," 9-44. January 11, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "Montana Rep," 9-51. February 8, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "Traitor of the Greasy Sack Pool," 9-52. March 22, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "Come All You Texas Rangers," 9-48. April 26, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "The Gallows Brand," 9-52. June 7, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "Border-Jumpin' Buscadero," 9-45. July 5, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "Lightnin' Branded," 22-59. August 16, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "Bullet Holes in the Plug Hat Range," 9-46. September 20, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "The Brush Poppers," 9-50. November 1, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "Caballeros of Doom," 9-52. December 13, 1941 (Box 13)
      - "Powdersmoke Pardners," 20-61. January 24, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Three Tough Hands," 18-64. February 21, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Snake River Rep," 9-47. March 21, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "The Devil Hate a Quitter," 9-50. April 25, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Dead Men's Hats," 9-50. May 30, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Gun Packer of the Circle C," 9-52. June 27, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Paid off in Bullets," 9-53. July 25, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Gun Slinger of the 7 Up," 9-52. August 22, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Renegade Buster," 9-46. October 17, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "The Horsehair Bridle," 9-50. November 14, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Gunsmoke Serenade," 9-44. December 12, 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Trail to Rancho Grande," 22-60. January 9, 1943 (Box 14)
      - "Law Comes to War Bonnet," 51-92. April 17, 1943 (Box 14)
      - "Kilbourn Bros.--Wolf Wranglers," 20-58. May 15, 1943 (Box 14)
      - "Trailing North to Trouble," 9-45. July 10, 1943 (Box 14)
      - "King of the Range," 6-36. February 5, 1944 (Box 14)
      - "Outlaws Make Dim Tracks," 6-32. February 19, 1944 (Box 14)
      - "Guns Welcome to Grass Hills," 6-31. March 1944 (Box 14)
      - "Driftin' Cowhand," 45-71. April 1944 (Box 14)
      - "When the Sign is Right," 6-32. May 1944 (Box 14)
      - "The Dogie Kid," 42-65. June 1944 (Box 14)
      - "The Coffee pot Boils Over," 36-58. July 1944 (Box 14)
      - "Hot Lead Cuts a Trail Herd," 34-58. August 1944 (Box 14)
      - "Stepsons of Hate," 38-61. September 1944 (Box 14)
      - "Rawson's Well," 33-58. October 1944 (Box 14)
      - "The Jelly Bean Trail," 7-29. November 1944 (Box 14)
      - "Law Rides to Lobo Valley," 6-32. December 1944 (Box 14)
      - "Satan's Segundo," 6-30. January 1945 (Box 14)
      - "The Circle Bar Kid," 6-29. February 1945 (Box 14)
      - "Renegade Ramrods," 5-30. March 1945 (Box 14)
      - "The San Pasquel Float," 6-29. April 1945 (Box 14)
      - "Bible Ben's Rep," 6-31. June 1945 (Box 14)
      - "The Man from Nowhere," 6-32. July 1945 (Box 14)
      - "The Long S Rep," 6-32. August 1945 (Box 14)
      - "Sons O' Texans," 6-32. September 1945 (Box 14)
      - "Texas Ranger's Long Reach," 6-31. October 1945 (Box 14)
      - "Bullet Marked," 6-31. November 1945 (Box 14)
      - "Trigger Tamed," 6-31. December 1945 (Box 14)
      - "Hank Garretson's Mistake," 6-27. January 1946 (Box 14)
      - "The Cibicu Kid," 6-31. February 1946 (Box 14)
      - "Cottontail," 6-29. March 1946 (Box 14)
      - " The Big Ramrod," 6-32. April 1946 (Box 14)
      - "Buckshot Payoff," 6-31. May 1946 (Box 14)
      - "The San Marcos Borderjumpers," 6-31. June 1946 (Box 14)
      - "Sleeper Sid's Tally," 6-31. July 1946 (Box 14)
      - "Lobo Gap," 40-65. September 1946 (Box 14)
      - "Trail Back to Trouble," 6-32. October 1946 (Box 14)
      - "The Tenderfoot," 56-82. Decmeber 1946 (Box 14)
      - "The Black Maverick," 34-57. January 1947 (Box 14)
      - "The Tough Teal Brand," 42-69. February 1947 (Box 14)
      - "Reppin' for the Dead," 6-31. March 1947 (Box 14)
      - "Powder River Pilgrim," 38-65. April 1947 (Box 14)
      - "Gun Seal on Rustler's Range," 66-91. May 1947 (Box 14)
      - "Sheeped-Out," 78-104. June 1947 (Box 14)
      - "Sky Pilot's Saga," 7-33. July 1947 (Box 14)
      - "The Muleshoe Jackpot," 82-109. August 1947 (Box 14)
      - "The Moccasin Kid," 46-74. September 1947 (Box 14)
      - "The T Down Ramrod," 78-104. October 1947 (Box 14)
      - "Pasear to Trouble," 88-113. November1947 (Box 14)
      - "Miracle at San Mateo," 7-33. December 1947 (Box 14)
      - "Payoff at Boundary Town," 82-109. January 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Tinhorn Rep," 42-68. February 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Showdown at the Narrows," 57-82. March 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Secret of Painted Rock," 62-87. April 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Tinhorn's Trigger Ties," 92-118. May 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Holed Up Under the Rim," 66-92. June 1948 (Box 14)
      - "The Lightening Brand," 18-44. July 1948 (Box 14)
      - "The Gotch-eared Roan," 106-132. "July 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Guns Across the Rio Grande," 110-136. September 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Windmill Kid," 14-42. October 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Rimrock Retribution," 110-159. November 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Driftin' South to Trouble," 48-66. December 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Homesteader's Havoc," 50-73. January 1949 (Box 14)
      - "Mr. Pell of the Muleshoe Bar," 16-42. February 1949 (Box 14)
      - "Loco Jones," 54-81. March 1949 (Box 14)
      - "3-7-77," 47-72. April 1949 (Box 14)
      - "The Secret of Adobe Corrals," 78-101. May 1949 (Box 14)
      - "Blizzard Rider," 50-75. June 1949 (Box 14)
      - "Winner Take All," 20-48. July 1949 (Box 14)
    - Western Story Magazine Annual
      - "Branded Arrow Pointed North," 28-51. 1941 (Box 15)
      - "Range of No Return," 3-29. 1943 (Box 15)
      - "Gun Boss of Powder River," 98-119. 1944 (Box 15)
      - "Lightin' Branded," 2-25. 1945 (Box 15)
      - "Dead Man's Hats," 67-90. 1946 (Box 15)
      - "Kilbourn Bros.--Wolf Wranglers," 2-108. 1948 (Box 15)
      - "Rawson's Well," 35-46. 1950 (Box 15)
    - Western Fiction Magazine
      - "Viglante Vengeance," 1/2: 4-17. October 1970 (Box 15)
    - Writers' Digest
      - "Rangeland Word Wrangler," 34-39. Article about Walt Coburn by Fred Gipson. September 1949 (Box 15)
    - Writers' Markets and Methods
      - "If You are Writing a Western: An Interview with Walt Coburn," XLII/3: 7-8. June 1939 (Box 15)
  - Scrapbooks, 1964-1974
    - Scrapbook # 1
      - "Tom Mix's Last Sundown," True West, 6-11. August-September 1968 (Box 16)
      - "The Loner," True West, 6-11. March-April 1969 (Box 16)
      - "Word Wrangler of the Old West," The Quarter Horse Journal, 138-316. May 1973 (Box 16)
    - Scrapbook # 2
      - "The Inimitable Breezy Cox," True West, 14-54. November-December 1967 (Box 16)
      - "He Lost His Youth in the Deer Lodge Pen," True West, 12-72. January-February 1968 (Box 16)
      - "Indestructable Johnnie Mullens," True West, 6-50. November-December 1966 (Box 16)
      - "Good Hearted and Unlucky," Old West, 8-60. Spring 1968 (Box 16)
      - "Wild Horse Roundup," Horse Tales, 12-18. Spring 1974 (Box 16)
      - "The Makin' of a Brush Popper Cowhand," Frontier Times, 8-14. October-November 1970 (Box 16)
      - "El Desecho," True West, 18-86. May-June 1970 (Box 16)
    - Scrapbook # 3
      - "One Thanksgiving Day," Old West, 22-57. Winter 1971 (Box 16)
      - "Tom Mix's Last Showdown," Frontier Times, 6-11. August-September 1968 (Box 16)
      - "Anklets of Pig Iron," Wanderlust, 8-54. Summer 1973 (Box 16)
      - "Shanghaied!" Old West, 16-45. Summer 1973 (Box 16)
      - "Riding to the Hounds, Prairie Style," Old West, 16-46. Winter 1970 (Box 16)
      - "A Lousy Ending to a Top-Notch Trail Drive," True West, 18-46. January-February 1970 (Box 16)
    - Scrapbook # 4
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Howdy!" True West, 17, 56. July-August 1965 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Humpy Jack Davis," Frontier Times, 17, 64. October-November 1965 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Charlie Brewster," True West, 31, 42. November-December 1965 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Tex Alvord," Frontier Times, 17, 61. August-September 1965 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Bill Lorne," True West, 13, 60. September-October 1965 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Gregory Doney," Frontier Times, 11, 45. December-January 1965 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Dead Eye Charlie," True West, 17, 62. January-February 1966 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Uncle Joe," True West, 21, 51. March-April 1966 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Cherokee Bob," True West, 11, 61. May-June 1966 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Deniff Boys," True West, 13, 48. July-August 1966 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "My Brother, Wallace," True West, 11, 56. September-October 1966 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Jake Myers," True West, 15, 53. January-February 1966 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Charlie Collins," Old West, 17, 50. Spring 1967 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Lyin' Frank," True West, 10-11, 56. May-June 1967 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "Snowflake," Frontier Times, 13, 67. June-July 1967 (Box 17)
      - Walt Colburn's Tally Book: "The Brown Horse Jug," Frontier Times, 14-15. October-November 1967 (Box 17)
      - "No Re-Ride," Old West, 31. Fall 1965 (Box 17)
      - "Prairie Fire," Old West, 7, 56. Winter 1966 (Box 17)
      - "The Night Dutch Henry Played Santa Claus," True West, 12-16, 33. September-October 1969 (Box 17)
      - "Line Camp Outlaw," True West, 6-9, 44, 65. March-April 1968 (Box 17)
      - "Powder!" Frontier Times, 6-9, 56-58. April-May 1966 (Box 17)
      - "The Honor of Old Thunder," Old West, 18-19, 58. Fall 1964 (Box 17)
      - "Blood Brothers," True West, 10-12, 44. March-April 1971 (Box 17)
    - Scrapbook # 5
      - "The Claim Jumpers," True West, 14-17, 44-46. July-August 1970 (Box 17)
      - "Frostbite and Shenanigans on the Zortman-Malta Line," Frontier Times, 6-9, 64-70. October-November 1968 (Box 17)
      - "Ruckus at Old Fort Musselshell," True West, 22-25, 58-60. July-August 1969 (Box 17)
      - "Fourth of July at Lodge Pole," Old West, 2-7, 47-53. Fall 1969 (Box 17)
      - "Christmas at Rocky Point," True West, 12-13, 52-53. November-December 1969 (Box 17)
    - Scrapbook # 6
      All Duplicates.
    - Scrapbook # 7
      - "Honor Among Horse Thieves," True West, 6-9, 66-68. July-August 1972 (Box 18)
      - "The Makin' of a Brush Popper Cowhand," Frontier Times, 8-11, 46. October-November 1970 (Box 18)
    - Scrapbook # 8
      - "Camp Cooks and Mail Order Brides," Frontier Times. February-March 1971 (Box 18)
      - "The Case of the Locoed horses," Frontier Times. December-January 1971 (Box 18)
      - "The Killing of Antoine Fiant," True West, 6-9, 41. May-June 1971 (Box 18)
      - "Bringing Home the Cook," True West, 10-19, 62. May-June 1971 (Box 18)
      - "Franchy the Bronc Rider," True West, 14-16, 52. September-October 1972 (Box 18)
      - "No Questions Asked," Frontier Times, 12-15, 49. February-March 1973 (Box 18)
      - "A Bunkhouse Confidence Man," Frontier Times, 6-9, 48. June-July 1968 (Box 18)
      - "The Wake of Whiskey Bill," Old West, 16-18, 58. Winter 1967 (Box 18)
      - "Repping With the Id Wagon," True West, 18-21, 48. January-February 1972 (Box 18)
      - "Law Rides the Larb Hills," Frontier Times, 6-9, 47. June-July 1972 (Box 18)
    - Scrapbook # 9
      All Dublicates.
  - Manuscripts, 1956-1974
    - Walt Coburn: Western Word Wrangler: Typescript. No Date (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Walt Coburn: Western Word Wrangler: Final Draft, 1-99. No Date (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Walt Coburn: Western Word Wrangler: Final Draft, 100-199. No Date (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Walt Coburn: Western Word Wrangler: Final Draft, 200-321. No Date (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Walt Coburn: Western Word Wrangler: Correspondence, Northland Press. No Date (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Walt Coburn: Western Word Wrangler: Reviews. No Date (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Typescript, 1-99. No Date (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Typescript, 101-200. No Date (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Typescript, 201-300. No Date (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Typescript, 301-368 and Appendix. No Date (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Micellaneous. No Date (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Holograph manuscript, (photocopies) "The Circle C Ranch." No Date (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Correspondence, University of Oklahoma. No Date (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Correspondence, Miscellaneous. 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Correspondence, Miscellaneous. 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Pioneer Cattleman in Montana: Reviews. No Date (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "Stirrup High," Correspondence, Julian Messner. 1956-1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - "Stirrup High," Correspondence, Miscellaneous. No Date (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - "Spur Wranglers" (proposed comic strip) Correspondence. No Date (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Short Stories (typescripts) "The Bullet Marked Saddle"; "The Caballero and the Lady Cow"; "County Kids"; "Forgotten Prayer"; "A Game Loser"; "The Gun That Had No Notches"; "The Hole Card"; "Night Ride"; "Red Robin"; and "Feud Valley." No Date (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous poems (typescripts). No Date (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Motion Pictures Scripts and Posters: Brand of the Black; Windmill Rawhide Halo Jack Hoxie (2 photographs and clippings); posters; and flyers (1 photograph). No Date (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous reviews: "Mavericks"; "Ringtailed Rannyhans"; "Sky-Pilot Cowboy"; and others. No Date (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1920-1975
  - Agents and Publishers, 1952-1975
    - Donald McCampbell. 1952-1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Donald McCampbell. 1960-1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Pollinger (British). 1954-1963 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Malcolm Reiss. 1940-1966 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous. 1945-1965 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Avon Books. 1965-1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - University Presses and Departments. 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Street and Smith Publications. 1939-1945 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Western Publications. 1956-1967 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Western Publications. 1968-1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous. 1922-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Topical, No Date
    - Kino Statue. 1963 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - E.J. McGilvra. 1964-1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - National Cowboy Hall of Fame. 1961-1967 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - National Geographic Magazine. 1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Montana Historical Society. 1948-1973 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - NEA Service, Inc. 1950 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Ross Santee (photocopies). 1957 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Roy George and Associates, (re: Tom Mix). 1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Arizona Highways. 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Western Writers of America. 1954-1962 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous. 1950s-1960s (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - General, 1920-1970
    - 1920-1939 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - 1940-1949 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - 1950-1959 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - 1970-1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Series III: Personal Material and Photographs, 1929-1974
  - Personal Material and Photographs, No Date
    - Biographical. 1920s-1960s (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous. 1940s-1970s (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings. 1929-1974 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Photographs (also in Box 28). 1920s-1960s (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Jack Dempsey (photographs, newsclippings). No Date (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Will Rogers (2 typed letters). 1927 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Personal Material: Financial and Miscellaneous Notebooks, No Date
    - Miscellaneous notebooks, bank books, accounts. No Date (Box 26)
  - Photographs, No Date
    - Portraits (oversize). No Date (Box 28)